
  <rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
      <title>Blog - Dijets</title>
      <link>https://dijets.io/blog</link>
      <description>Latest news from Dijets</description>
      <language>en</language>
      <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
      <atom:link href="https://dijets.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
      <item>
  <guid>https://dijets.io/enterprises/banking</guid>
  <title>Operate with more liquidity and speed using digital assets. Automate compliance processes through immutable data records &amp; accelerate settlements between institutions.</title>
  <link>https://dijets.io/enterprises/banking</link>
  <description>Purpose built ECC Engines for industry-wide considerations can simplify digital assets, tokenisation, and DeFi for institutional-grade implementation.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://dijets.io/enterprises/healthcare</guid>
  <title>Improve efficiency, interoperability &amp; supply chain traceability while reducing administrative costs, fraud &amp; errors in medical billing.</title>
  <link>https://dijets.io/enterprises/healthcare</link>
  <description>Blockchain tech can offer everything healthcare companies need to create innovative products and services while building trust in the healthcare system.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://dijets.io/enterprises/supply-chains</guid>
  <title>Learn how your supply chain can use data to handle the disruptions of today and build resiliency for the future.</title>
  <link>https://dijets.io/enterprises/supply-chains</link>
  <description>Supply chain data is not always visible, available or trusted. Businesses and consumers want brands to guarantee product authenticity, while supply chain participants demand responsible sourcing and better visibility to minimise disputes.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://dijets.io/enterprises/insurance</guid>
  <title>As customers demand modern business practices &amp; faster settlements, insurance providers must adopt new technologies to survive.</title>
  <link>https://dijets.io/enterprises/insurance</link>
  <description>Imagine an immutable database that contains the policy information of every driver on the road today. When a wreck occurs, a police report is loaded to that database, repair estimates follow shortly after, and payments are distributed via this automated system.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://dijets.io/enterprises/public-sector</guid>
  <title>Governments can reduce time, cost &amp; risk in regulatory compliance, voting transparency, identity management and citizen services.</title>
  <link>https://dijets.io/enterprises/public-sector</link>
  <description>Governments can accelerate their drive to net-zero emissions, ensure voting transparency, handle cross-agency HR functions &amp; enhance financial transaction management, asset management, contract management and regulatory compliance &amp; build trust with citizens.</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://dijets.io/enterprises/legal-sector</guid>
  <title>Legal firms can streamline, re-engineer, automate, disintermediate, and secure many of legal processes without losing any of the judicial authority.</title>
  <link>https://dijets.io/enterprises/legal-sector</link>
  <description>Blockchain enables legal firms to securely and transparently manage legal agreements and transform paper contracts into programmable, self-executing actions.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://dijets.io/enterprises/education</guid>
  <title>Operate with more liquidity and speed using digital assets. Automate compliance processes through immutable data records &amp; accelerate settlements between institutions.</title>
  <link>https://dijets.io/enterprises/education</link>
  <description>Purpose built ECC Engines for industry-wide considerations can simplify digital assets, tokenisation, and DeFi for institutional-grade implementation.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://dijets.io/enterprises/music</guid>
  <title>Streamlined royalty payments, usage-based billing models, decreased IP infringement, and direct monetisation of all copywritten assets.</title>
  <link>https://dijets.io/enterprises/music</link>
  <description>Digital piracy, fraudulent copies, infringed studio intellectual property (IP), and duplication of digital items cost upwards of an estimated $95 billion annually.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://dijets.io/enterprises/esg-metrics</guid>
  <title>Blockchain can report environmental impact in detail, automate the report, &amp; also preserve the records. This gives consumers, managers, and investors more visibility into the practices of a company.</title>
  <link>https://dijets.io/enterprises/esg-metrics</link>
  <description>In a time when consumers are demanding value-based companies and products and when building, managing, and reporting on environmental, social, and governance (ESG) initiatives is becoming crucial for organisations, distributed ledger technology provides the best path forward.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://dijets.io/enterprises/construction</guid>
  <title>Learn how Dijets can facilitate innovation in construction through smart contracts. By shifting current payment &amp; project management systems towards a more transparent &amp; fair practice.</title>
  <link>https://dijets.io/enterprises/construction</link>
  <description>Supply chain data is not always visible, available or trusted. Businesses and consumers want brands to guarantee product authenticity, while supply chain participants demand responsible sourcing and better visibility to minimise disputes.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://dijets.io/enterprises/food-and-beverages</guid>
  <title>Dijets can enable products in the food and beverage industry to be tracked transparently throughout their entire life cycle – from the field all the way to the kitchen.</title>
  <link>https://dijets.io/enterprises/food-and-beverages</link>
  <description>Blockchain and Food Supply</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://dijets.io/enterprises/manufacturing</guid>
  <title>Buffeted by intricate sourcing arrangements, fluctuating demand &amp; counterfeit parts manufacturers today face significant challenges in operating complex supply chains.</title>
  <link>https://dijets.io/enterprises/manufacturing</link>
  <description>Purpose built ECC Engines for industry-wide considerations can simplify manufacturing industry issues.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://dijets.io/enterprises/gaming</guid>
  <title>Learn how Gaming can take advantage of Dijets ECCs and run dedicated networks for specialised gaming usecases.</title>
  <link>https://dijets.io/enterprises/gaming</link>
  <description>Blockchain and Real Estate</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://dijets.io/enterprises/recruitment</guid>
  <title>Digitise legacy systems and job boards that protect your candidates database and offers traceability.</title>
  <link>https://dijets.io/enterprises/recruitment</link>
  <description>Blockchain and Recruitment</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://dijets.io/enterprises/real-estate</guid>
  <title>Use Dijets Utility Chain to offer fractional ownership of real estate by digitising property ownership.</title>
  <link>https://dijets.io/enterprises/real-estate</link>
  <description>Blockchain and Real Estate</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

    </channel>
  </rss>
